A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Catalogued Reports, Reports 6262-9286 FA739C
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Big brother's last stand: George Washington University (Reports 009275), 1970 (Box 384)
  Indians; Indian's rights; Levitan, Sar A.
- North Africa Field Office quarterly reports, December 1969 through (Reports 009276), 1972 (Box 385)
  1 v.;var. pag.: tables -- 28 cm.
  Technical assistance -- Africa, North; Endowments -- Africa, North -- Evaluation; Ford Foundation. Middle East and Africa; Ford Foundation
- North Africa Field Office quarterly reports, July 1973 through (Reports 009277) (Box 385)
- Access to Foundation records: policy and procedures (Reports 009278), 1974 (Box 385)
  Administration/Library
  Access policy; Archival records; Ford Foundation
- The development of the social sciences in Indonesia (Reports 009279), undated
  Social sciences -- Indonesia; Schlegel, Stuart A.
- A brief calendar of events and some comments on the social sciences in Central America (Reports 009280), 1971
  Social sciences -- Central America; Blair, Calvin P.
- Ford Foundation oral history project: policy on access to material (Reports 009281), 1974 (Box 385)
- Records operations (Reports 009282), undated (Box 385)
  Archival records; Records storage; Jones, Eldon L.
- Maintenance of inactive records (Reports 009283), undated (Box 385)
  Archival records; Records storage; Newhall, Ann C.
- Maintenance of archival records (Reports 009284), undated (Box 385)
- Saudi Arabia Project quarterly report (Reports 009285), 1970 (Box 385)
  Administrative agencies -- Saudi Arabia -- Management; Public administration -- Saudi Arabia; Technical assistance -- Saudi Arabia; Ford Foundation
- Ford Foundation meeting held Monday, July 17, 1967 from 8:45-10:45 p.m. at the Plaza Hotel, New York City (Reports 009286) (Box 385)
  220 leaves -- 28 cm.
  Charitable uses, trusts, and foundations -- United States -- Congresses; Ford Foundation